

# **JAMES RIADY**

Software Engineer

0	Jl. P. Cermin No. 51, Perbaungan
	+62 821 6567 9711
$\boxtimes$	jamesriady1998@yahoo.com
	saengdaet

## **BIOGRAPHY**

James Riady is a Software Engineer with 3+ years experience in developing web-based applications. Experienced in using Java, Go, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Laravel, and Vue JS. He is currently working at Shopee Indonesia as Backend Engineer. He also likes to help others on Stackoverflow when he has free time.

### **EXPERIENCE**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (01.2020) SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN (10.2019 - 01.2020) SHOPEE (ID)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (09.2018 - 01.2020) TOP REMIT

CO-FOUNDER (09.2017 - 12.2018) LEMON HEXA

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER (12.2017 - 08.2018) DARKOTECH MANDIRI INDONESIA



## EDUCATION

INFORMATION SYSTEM STUDENT (09.2015 - 11.2019) UNIVERSITAS PELITA HARAPAN

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL (06.2012 - 04.2015) SMA METHODIST EL-SHADDAY



## LANGUAGES





## **INTERESTS**







## SKILLS

Java	••••	HTML&CSS	••••
JavaScript	••••	Vue JS	••••
Jquery		React JS	
Laravel		MySQL	••••
Go			



## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

NOVEMBER 2020 TOP 30 | Telkomsel Tech Titans League Series 1 JAKARTA

OCTOBER 2017 3RD POSITION | BNI HACKFEST MEDAN